Litchfield County judicial records
Litchfield Historical Society
- Subject files
  - Taverns, Plymouth, Washington, 1856-1860 (Folder 136)
  - Taverns, Watertown, Winchester, 1856-1860 (Folder 137)
  - Miscellaneous, Mt. Tom road survey, 1840 Apr 20
    Surveyed by Seth Catlin. This oversize item is currently stored in 18B box 20.
  - delete